smhos.org 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Salvation Ministries

**Privacy, Shipping, Billing, Return Policy, Terms of Use, and Contact**

Salvation Ministries is committed to maintaining your trust and confidence. The following online privacy policy is intended to protect and secure the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified) you provide to us online.

In addition, Salvation Ministries will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. We may periodically send you e-mail announcing news and event information. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from us as well.

**No Sharing of Personal Information**

Salvation Ministries never sells, rents, leases or exchanges your personal information with other organizations. Salvation Ministries assures you that the identity of all who contact us through this Web site will be kept confidential. Salvation Ministries may occasionally send mailings on behalf of other organizations or ministries when their interests align with Salvation Ministries.

**Security**

Salvation Ministries is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have established and implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Salvation Ministries uses Internet Encryption Software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Protocol when collecting or transferring sensitive data. Any information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, and then de-encrypted at our server. Once we receive your information, it is accessible only to a small number of trusted Salvation Ministries employees who have been specially trained in processing this information.

**Cookies**

From time to time, we may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can’t read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you when you return to our sites, or to identify which areas of our network of Web sites you have visited (i.e. e-commerce sites, etc.). We may use this information to better personalize the content you see on our sites.

Many Web sites place cookies on your hard drive. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Your browser can refuse all cookies, or show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**Managing cookies**

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a)    <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en> (Chrome);

(b)    <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences> (Firefox);

(c)    <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/> (Opera);

(d)    <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies> (Internet Explorer);

(e)    <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411> (Safari); and

(f)     <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy> (Edge).

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

Financial transactions relating to our website and services are OR may be handled by our payment services providers, PayU, Paypal, Kindrid, Ravepay, GTPay. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers’ privacy policies and practices at their respective websites.

In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data mentioned earlier, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

**Amendments**

We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.

We may notify you of significant changes to this policy by email or through our website.

**Contacting Us**

If you have comments or questions about any of our policies or our website, please contact us. For information and enquires please contact us at (+234) 815 -0190040. 

Salvation Ministries, International Headquarters – Plot 17 Birabi Street, GRA, Phase 1, Port Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria

You can contact us:

(a)    by post, to the postal address given above;

(b)    using our website contact form;

(c)    by telephone, on the contact number published on our website from time to time

(d)    by email, using the email address published on our website from time to time.
